{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"3899","name":"College for Creative Studies","address":"485 W Milwaukee Ave","zipcode":"48202","owner":"Sodexo Management Inc.","licenseNumber":"202846","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","coords":"-83.07514,42.36775","geojson":{"id":"3899","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.075137831,42.3677520750001]},"properties":{"name":"College for Creative Studies","owner":"Sodexo Management Inc.","address":"485 W Milwaukee Ave","zipcode":"48202","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"202846","establishmentid":"3899","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180.0","most_recent_license_date":"4/30/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"3627","name":"The Coffee Shop & Deli","address":"3044 W Grand Blvd., Ste. 1429","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"1712","name":"JCE Acquisitions, LLC  DBA Subway ","address":"3044 W Grand Blvd","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"51622872","name":"Runabout Cafe","address":"3044 W Grand Blvd","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"662","name":"Northern Lights Lounge","address":"660 W Baltimore St","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"4170","name":"New Center Park","address":"2998 W Grand Blvd","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"51622570","name":"Avalon Cafe and Biscuit Bar","address":"2990 W Grand Blvd","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"4878","name":"Cafe Con Leche - Nord","address":"2990 W Grand Blvd","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"2165","name":"New Center Eatery","address":"3100 W Grand Blvd","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"2241","name":"La Musique/Hotel St. Regis","address":"3071 W Grand Blvd","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"51622711","name":"St. Regis Operating LLC","address":"3071 W Grand Blvd","zipcode":"48236"},{"establishmentid":"2076","name":"The Coney Man","address":"3031 W Grand Blvd. ","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"1535","name":"Detroit Donuts","address":"3031 W Grand Blvd","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"2287","name":"Lunchtime Neo LLC","address":"3031 W Grand Blvd. Suite 201","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"2616","name":"New Center-Rice Bowl","address":"3031 W Grand Blvd., Suite 230","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"4748","name":"New Center Grill","address":"3031 W Grand Blvd., Suite 202","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"1683","name":"Coffee Master","address":"3031 W Grand Blvd. #206","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"1722","name":"New Center Gourmet","address":"3031 W Grand Blvd. Ste 134","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"4119","name":"Motown Coney Island","address":"6501 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"3793","name":"University Preparatory Academy Elem","address":"435 Amsterdam","zipcode":"48202"},{"establishmentid":"5413","name":"Franklin Wright Settlement Inc.","address":"7375 Woodward Ave","zipcode":"48202"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"42155","inspectionDate":"2018-05-07T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"CAFETERIA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"40345","inspectionDate":"2017-10-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"2-201.11","violationDescription":"The PERMIT HOLDER shall require FOOD EMPLOYEE applicants and  FOOD EMPLOYEES to report to the PERSON IN CHARGE,  information about their health and activities as they relate to diseases that are transmissible through FOOD. AND report the information in a manner that allows the PERSON IN CHARGE to prevent the likelihood of foodborne disease transmission.(P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Fail to require employees to report illness as rule requires","subProblem":"","location":"EMPLOYEE(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Require reporting as stated above."},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"LOUNGE TWELVE","subLocation":"Cooler (Simply To Go)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"CAFETERIA","subLocation":"Cooler (Simply To Go)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"CAFETERIA","subLocation":"SAUTE STATION","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-11T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."},{"violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"CAFETERIA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"40346","inspectionDate":"2017-10-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"38920","inspectionDate":"2017-06-08T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"37327","inspectionDate":"2016-11-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"SIMPLY TO GO ROOM","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"ARGONAUT GRILL","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"},{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"SALAD BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"ARGONAUT GRILL","subLocation":"Cooler(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."}]},{"inspectionid":"36964","inspectionDate":"2016-10-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not safe","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER (PRODUCE)","subLocation":"EXPIRED DATE MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-18T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"3899"}}